Preliminary Guide to the Mobius Advertising Awards Collection, [1970s]-2002, bulk 1984-2002 RL.00902
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Mobius Advertising Awards collection
1970s-2002, bulk 1984-2002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Mobius Advertising Awards
RL.00902
1328 Linear Feet
19,024 Items
Access Restrictions
Access restricted. Collection is currently being processed and will not be available for research until use copies are made and indexed.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Library received the collection as a gift from Mobius in 1997-2004.
Historical Note
The Mobius Advertising Awards were first presented in 1971 for excellence in television, radio, and print advertising, as well as package design.
Collection Overview
Collection consists primarily of television commercials, although it includes some radio commercials, which were entered for Mobius awards presented in 1971-1999. Most of the collection is divided into two main series, North America and International. Commercials are judged by product type/category as well as budget size. Also included are brochures and press releases which describe the award process ca. 1970s-1990s (98-156 box 68). There are compilation tapes documenting the award-winning entries for 1990-1997 (98-156 box 69). (Accessions 1997-0101: 12,237 items, 850.5 linear feet, dated 1984-1991, undated; 1998-0156: 1500 items, 105 linear feet, dated 1971-1997; 1999-0152: 1200 items, 112.5 linear feet, dated 1997-1998). An encoded container list has not been created for these additions. Please consult the paper finding aids located in the repository.
The addition (1999-0440) (1100 items, 117 linear feet; dated 1998) consists entirely of videotaped television commercial entries for Mobius awards presented in 1999; the commercials aired in 1998. The collection is divided into two main series: North American and International. The tapes are then ordered according to product type/category (105 in all) ranging from automotive, children's products, commercial products, food, home care, set design, talent, and others. The entries document what ad agencies feel are their best works from the U.S. and abroad.
The addition (2001-0156) (1373 items, 88 linear feet; dated 2000) consists of 1072 videotaped television commercial entries for Mobius awards, most likely presented in 2000. The collection is divided into two main series: North American and International. In addition there are 285 cassettes and 16 reel-to-reel audiotapes containing radio advertising entries, also divided into North American and International categories. The entries document what ad agencies feel are their best works from the U.S. and abroad.
The addition (2002-0187) (816 items, 31 linear feet; dated 2001) consists of videotaped television commercial entries for the 2001 Mobius Awards. The collection is divided into two main series: North American and International. The video cassettes are mainly BetacamSP. There are also 176 audiocassettes containing radio commercials and 13 electronic documents on 7 CD-ROMs. Each entry is assigned a code that indicates the category in which it was entered in the competition.
The addition (2004-0103) (705 items; 27 linear feet; dated 2002) consists of videotaped television commercial entries for the 2002 Mobius Awards. The collection is divided into two main series: North American and International. The video cassettes are mainly VHS and BetacamSP. There are also 119 CD-ROMs. Eight audiocassettes contain radio commercials. Each entry is assigned a code that indicates the category in which it was entered in the competition.
Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Audiotapes; Videocassettes; Television advertising; Machine-readable records; Audiocassettes; Advertising -- History; Mobius Advertising Awards; Mobius Advertising Awards; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Accession 1999-0440
  Scope and Contents note
  Category numbers refer to subject ( product-type) or technical categories of entries. Not all categories are represented in this accession, especially among the international entries. See printed finding aid for a listing of categories.
  - North American Television Entries on videotape (Category number)
    - 1 (Box 1)
    - 1 (Box 2)
    - 1 (Box 3)
    - 1 (Box 4)
    - 1 (Box 5)
    - 1 (Box 6)
    - 1 (Box 7)
    - 1-3 (Box 8)
    - 4-5 (Box 9)
    - 5-12 (Box 10)
    - 12-17 (Box 11)
    - 17-21 (Box 12)
    - 21-24 (Box 13)
    - 24-26 (Box 14)
    - 26-28 (Box 15)
    - 28-30 (Box 16)
    - 29-30 (Box 17)
    - 30-42 (Box 18)
    - 42-48 (Box 19)
    - 49-51 (Box 20)
    - 51-54 (Box 21)
    - 55-56 (Box 22)
    - 56-58 (Box 23)
    - 58-59 (Box 24)
    - 59-60 (Box 25)
    - 60-61 (Box 26)
    - 61-63 (Box 27)
    - 63-67 (Box 28)
    - 67-68 (Box 29)
    - 68-69 (Box 30)
    - 69 (Box 31)
    - 69-73 (Box 32)
    - 73-74 (Box 33)
    - 75-78 (Box 34)
    - 78-81 (Box 35)
    - 81 (Box 36)
    - 81-82 (Box 37)
    - 82-84 (Box 38)
    - 84 (Box 39)
    - 84 (Box 40)
    - 84-86 (Box 41)
    - 85-86 (Box 42)
    - 86 (Box 43)
    - 86 (Box 44)
    - 86-89 (Box 45)
    - 89-92 (Box 46)
    - 92-93 (Box 47)
    - 93-95 (Box 48)
    - 95-98 (Box 49)
    - 98-100 (Box 50)
    - 100-103 (Box 51)
    - 103-105 (Box 52)
    - 105 (Box 53)
    - 105-107 (Box 54)
  - International Television Entries (Category number)
    - 1 (Box 55)
    - 1 (Box 56)
    - 2-20 (Box 57)
    - 21-26 (Box 58)
    - 26-30 (Box 59)
    - 31-39 (Box 60)
    - 40-56 (Box 61)
    - 57-65 (Box 62)
    - 66-73 (Box 63)
    - 73-75 (Box 64)
    - 76-84 (Box 65)
    - 84-85 (Box 66)
    - 86-93 (Box 67)
    - 93-94 (Box 68)
    - 95-103 (Box 69)
    - 103-105 (Box 70)
  - Mixed categories (Box 71)
  - North American Winners (Box 72)
  - North American Winners (Box 73)
  - North American Winners (Box 74)
  - North American Winners (Box 75)
  - North American Winners (Box 76)
  - International Winners (Box 77)
  - International Winners (Box 78)
- Accession 2001-0165
  Category numbers refer to subject (product-type) or technical categories of entries. Not all categories are represented in this accession, especially among the international entries. See printed finding aid in repository for a listing of categories.
  - North American Television Entries on videotape (Category number)
    - 1 (Box 1)
    - 1 (Box 2)
    - 1 (Box 3)
    - 1 (Box 4)
    - 1 (Box 5)
    - 1-2 (Box 6)
    - 2-4 (Box 7)
    - 4-5 (Box 8)
    - 5 (Box 9)
    - 6-7, 9 (Box 10)
    - 10-11, 13 (Box 11)
    - 13-14, 16-17 (Box 12)
    - 17 (Box 13)
    - 20 (Box 14)
    - 20-21 (Box 15)
    - 21 (Box 16)
    - 21-23 (Box 17)
    - 23-24, 26 (Box 18)
    - 26 (Box 19)
    - 26-27 (Box 20)
    - 28-29 (Box 21)
    - 29 (Box 22)
    - 29-30 (Box 23)
    - 32-36 (Box 24)
    - 37-40 (Box 25)
    - 40-42 (Box 26)
    - 43, 45-46, 48-49 (Box 27)
    - 50-51 (Box 28)
    - 51-52 (Box 29)
    - 52-54 (Box 30)
    - 54 (Box 31)
    - 54-56 (Box 32)
    - 56-58 (Box 33)
    - 58 (Box 34)
    - 58-59 (Box 35)
    - 59 (Box 36)
    - 59 (Box 37)
    - 59-60 (Box 38)
    - 60-61 (Box 39)
    - 61 (Box 40)
    - 61 (Box 41)
    - 61 (Box 42)
    - 61 (Box 43)
    - 61, 63 (Box 44)
    - 63-64, 66 (Box 45)
    - 66 (Box 46)
    - 66 (Box 47)
    - 66 (Box 48)
    - 66-67 (Box 49)
    - 67-68 (Box 50)
    - 68-69 (Box 51)
    - 70-73 (Box 52)
    - 73-74 (Box 53)
    - 74 (Box 54)
    - 74-75, 77 (Box 55)
    - 77-78 (Box 56)
    - 78-79 (Box 57)
    - 79-81 (Box 58)
    - 81 (Box 59)
    - 81 (Box 60)
    - 81-82 (Box 61)
    - 82 (Box 62)
    - 84 (Box 63)
    - 84 (Box 64)
    - 84 (Box 65)
    - 84 (Box 66)
    - 84 (Box 67)
    - 84-85 (Box 68)
    - 85 (Box 69)
    - 85-86 (Box 70)
    - 86 (Box 71)
    - 86 (Box 72)
    - 86 (Box 73)
    - 86 (Box 74)
    - 86 (Box 75)
    - 86 (Box 76)
    - 86, 90 (Box 77)
    - 90-92 (Box 78)
    - 92-94 (Box 79)
    - 94 (Box 80)
    - 94-95 (Box 81)
    - 95-96 (Box 82)
    - 96, 98 (Box 83)
    - 98-99 (Box 84)
    - 99-100 (Box 85)
    - 100-101 (Box 86)
    - 101, 103-104 (Box 87)
    - 104-105 (Box 88)
    - 105-106 (Box 89)
    - 106 (Box 90)
    - 106, 108, Mixed categories (Box 91)
  - International Television entries on videotape (Category number)
    - 1 (Box 92)
    - 1 (Box 93)
    - 1 (Box 94)
    - 1-5 (Box 95)
    - 10, 11, 12, 13, 19, 20 (Box 95A)
    - 20 (Box 96)
    - 20-23 (Box 97)
    - 23-24, 26 (Box 98)
    - 26-27 (Box 99)
    - 28-30 (Box 100)
    - 30, 32 (Box 101)
    - 32, 34, 36, 40-41, 43, 49 (Box 102)
    - 45-46, 49-51, 54 (Box 103)
    - 54-55 (Box 104)
    - 55-57 (Box 105)
    - 57-59, 61 (Box 106)
    - 63-64, 66 (Box 107)
    - 66 (Box 108)
    - 66-67 (Box 109)
    - 67 (Box 110)
    - 68-69, 73 (Box 111)
    - 73 (Box 112)
    - 73 (Box 113)
    - 73-74 (Box 114)
    - 74-75, 77 (Box 115)
    - 77-80 (Box 116)
    - 80-81 (Box 117)
    - 81-84 (Box 118)
    - 84 (Box 119)
    - 84-85 (Box 120)
    - 85-87 (Box 121)
    - 93-94 (Box 122)
    - 94-95 (Box 123)
    - 95-96 (Box 124)
    - 96 (Box 125)
    - 97, 99-101 (Box 126)
    - 101, 104 (Box 127)
    - 104-106 (Box 128)
    - 108 and Mixed categories (Box 129)
  - Radio Entries (All categories)
    - North American cassettes (Box 130-140)
    - International cassettes (Box 141-144)
    - North American and International reel-to-reel audiotapes (Box 145)
- Accession 2002-0187
  - North American Television Entries on videotape (Category number)
    - 1 (Box 1)
    - 1 (Box 2)
    - 1-3 (Box 3)
    - 4-7 (Box 4)
    - 9-20 (Box 5)
    - 20-26 (Box 6)
    - 26-29 (Box 7)
    - 29-38 (Box 8)
    - 38-43 (Box 9)
    - 44-50 (Box 10)
    - 50-57 (Box 11)
    - 57-59 (Box 12)
    - 59-60 (Box 13)
    - 60-61 (Box 14)
    - 61-66 (Box 15)
    - 67-69 (Box 16)
    - 69-73 (Box 17)
    - 74-78 (Box 18)
    - 79-81 (Box 19)
    - 81-84 (Box 20)
    - 84 (Box 21)
    - 84 (Box 22)
    - 84 (Box 23)
    - 86 (Box 24)
    - 86-91 (Box 25)
    - 93 (Box 26)
    - 99-104 (Box 27)
    - 104-106 (Box 28)
    - 106-108 (Box 29)
    - 108, 92, 84, no. # and duplicate (Box 30)
  - International Television Entries on videotape (Category number)
    - 1 (Box 31)
    - 1-20 (Box 32)
    - 20-24 (Box 33)
    - 24-29 (Box 34)
    - 29-30 (Box 35)
    - 30-37 (Box 36)
    - 40-44 (Box 37)
    - 45-52 (Box 38)
    - 52-61 (Box 39)
    - 61-68 (Box 40)
    - 69-80 (Box 41)
    - 81-84 (Box 42)
    - 84-91 (Box 43)
    - 94 (Box 44)
    - 94-95 (Box 45)
    - 95-98 (Box 46)
    - 99-101 (Box 47)
    - 101-106 (Box 48)
    - 106-108 (and combined) (Box 49)
  - North American Radio Entries on audio cassette tape (Category number)
    - 1-14 (Box 50)
    - 17-34 (Box 51)
    - 43-66 (Box 52)
    - 67-82 (Box 53)
    - 82-96 (Box 54)
    - 96-107 (Box 55)
  - International Radio Entries on audio cassette tape (Category number)
    - 1-67 (Box 56)
    - 68-89 (Box 57)
    - 93-107 and no. # (Box 58)
  - North American Television Entries on videotape (Category number)
    - Original Tapes category 1-39 (Box 59)
    - Original Tapes category 45-86 (Box 60)
    - Original Tapes category 90-104 and unmarked (Box 61)
  - International Television Entries on videotape (Category number)
    - Original Tapes category 1-94 (Box 62)
    - Original Tapes category 94-104 and mixed (Box 63)
    - Original Tapes (2) category unmarked (Box 64)
  - North American and International Television Entries on video tape (Category number)
    - Award Winners (Box 64 (cont.))
  - North American and International Radio Entries on audio cassette tape (Category number)
    - Original Tapes (Box 65)
    - Award Winners (Box 65)
- Accession 2004-0103
  Contains entries submitted for the 2002 Mobius awards competition. Category numbers refer to subject (product-type) or technical categories of entries. Not all categories are represented in this accession, especially among the international entries. See printed finding aid in repository for a listing of categories.
  - North American Television Entries on videotape (Category number)
    - 1 (Box 1)
    - 1 (Box 2)
    - 1 (Box 3)
    - 1 (Box 4)
    - 1,3,4,6 (Box 5)
    - 6,7,11,14,16,17 (Box 6)
    - 17,21,22 (Box 7)
    - 22-26 (Box 8)
    - 27-29 (Box 9)
    - 29-34 (Box 10)
    - 38-42, 50 (Box 11)
    - 52,54,57,59,61,62 (Box 12)
    - 62,64-66,68 (Box 13)
    - 68-70 (Box 14)
    - 70,74,75,80 (Box 15)
    - 80-82, 85 (Box 16)
    - 85-88 (Box 17)
    - 91, 93, 95-98 (Box 18)
    - 99-101 (Box 19)
    - 101-104 (Box 20)
    - 104 (Box 21)
    - 104-106, 110, 111 (Box 22)
    - 111-116 (Box 23)
    - 117, 119, 120 (Box 24)
    - 120, 121, 123, 125, 126 (Box 25)
    - 126, 128 (Box 26)
  - International Television Entries on videotape (Category number)
    - 1 (Box 27)
    - 1, 2, 4-6, 8, 10, 14, 16, 18, 21 (Box 28)
    - 21-27 (Box 29)
    - 27-29, 30, 34, 35, 38 (Box 30)
    - 39, 41-46, 48-50 (Box 31)
    - 50, 52, 54, 58-60, 62, 65-69 (Box 32)
    - 69, 73, 75, 77, 79-81, 84, 85 (Box 33)
    - 85, 86, 91, 93, 99 (Box 34)
    - 99-101, 103, 104 (Box 35)
    - 104, 106, 107, 113, 114, 117 (Box 36)
    - 117, 121, 123, 126, 128 (Box 37)
    - 128, 130 (Box 38)
  - North American Internet Entry on videotape (Category number)
    - 1 (Box 38)
  - International Internet Entry on videotape (Category number)
    - 128 (Box 38)
  - North American Radio Entry on audio cassette and CD (Category number)
    - 1, 3, 21-23, 27, 30, 33, 35, 39, 62, 64, 68, 69, 73, 75 (Box 39)
    - 80, 82, 84-87, 91-93, 99, 113, 120, 127, 129, 130 (Box 40)
  - International Radio Entry on audio cassette and CD (Category number)
    - 1, 5, 18, 47, 52, 57, 61, 62, 64, 90, 98-100, 104 (Box 40)
- Accession 1997-051, 1985-1989; 1
  - Manitoba Government, Manitoba Community Services, "Wife Abuse; #1", "Wife Abuse #2", "Wife Abuse #3", R.K.W. Advertising Limited; Mobius category: 71; Mobius identifier: XT29ABC-71-U-85-C, 1985 February 26; 1
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0018)
  - TV Single Category #72/Sales Event, Crown Auto, Paragon Co. "Remco/STP/Robker", CRWN-5036 :30; Mobius category: 72; Mobius identifier: XT523-72-U-85-U, 1985 September 23; 2
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0009)
  - Client: Greater Detroit Chamber of Commerce, Agency: Young & Rubicam, Title: Arson, Length: 30; Mobius category: 71; Mobius identifier: XT685-71-U-85-U, 1985 October 15; 3
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0020)
  - Teledyne, "Sounds Good", J. Walter Thompson; Mobius category: 42; Mobius identifier: XT1549-42-U-85-C, circa 1985; 4
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0006)
  - Abby At The Museum,: 30 Seconds; Mobius category: 82; Mobius identifier: XT159-82-U-85-U, circa 1985; 5
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0007)
  - Pimlico Race Course, 1) Chase :30, 2) Rescue :30, W.B. Doner and Company; Mobius category: 49; Mobius identifier: XT1774AB-49-U-85-U, circa 1985; 6
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0008)
  - WWWE/RADIO 11, WWTV-5300 "News", :30; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT736-73-U-85-C, circa 1985; 7
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0010)
  - WWWE/RADIO 11, WWTV-5302 "Sports", :30; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT738-73-U-85-C, circa 1985; 8
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0011)
  - Stanley Steemer, QSFG-4304, "Whirl Away", :30; Mobius category: 36; Mobius identifier: XT740-36-U-85-U, circa 1985; 9
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0012)
  - Intoxicated Driving, TV Campaign, Category 71, Public Service Announcements, "Junkyard Ghosts", "Girlfriend", "Grieving Parents"; Mobius category: 71; Mobius identifier: XT524ABC-71-U-85-U, circa 1985; 10
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0013)
  - San Francisco Rag Shop, "Avenue Attitudes", :30; Mobius category: 10A; Mobius identifier: XT449-10A-U-85-U, circa 1985; 11
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0019)
  - Miller High Life, "Will to Win", :30, MOWP 2730, J. Walter Thompson, #621; Mobius category: 85; Mobius identifier: XT109-85-0-86-U, 1986 May 14; 12
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0036)
  - Turner Broadcasting System, CNN Anchor Testimonials, Libya, :30; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1064-73-U-86-U, 1986 September 17; 13
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0021)
  - :30 Second Spot, Yes...It's a Chevy; Mobius category: 85; Mobius identifier: XT203-85-0-86-U, 1986 September 19; 14
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0023)
  - Old 056, "Red Sticker Sale-Teaser" :30; Old 057C "Red Sticker Sale/Woman", :30; Mobius category: 2; Mobius identifier: XT547AB-2-0-86-U, 1986 September 25; 15
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0025)
  - C&R Clothiers, "Elevator" TV Entry, 3/4" NTSC Dub, Orion Enterprises; Mobius category: 72; Mobius identifier: XT1017-72-0-86-U, 1986 September 29; 16
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0028)
  - Jackie Cooper Enterprises, JCN-86-7-30-17-B11, JCB-86-7-30-11-B5, JCR-86-7-30-B13; Transmedia Comm. Entries; Mobius category: 80; Mobius identifier: XT1434ABC-80-U-86-U, 1986 October 08; 17
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0017)
  - Procter & Gamble Inc., Crest, "Pump", :30; Mobius category: 39; Mobius identifier: XT459-39-U-86-C, circa 1986; 18
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0014)
  - Columbia Gas, "Ice Cube", "Mark Of Efficiency", "Heating Dealer", 3 x :30, Lord, Sullivan & Yoder, INC.; Mobius category: 59; Mobius identifier: XT79ABC-59-U-86-U, circa 1986; 19
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0015)
  - Entry No. XT96, "Anniversary", Writer: Monica Byrne, Camera/Editor/Director: Kirk Reynolds, Lighting/Audio: Mark Guzman, Runs 30 Seconds; Mobius category: 72; Mobius identifier: XT96-72-U-86-U, circa 1986; 20
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 63, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0016)
  - Coca-Cola, "Grandfather", :45; Mobius category: 84; Mobius identifier: XT1284-84-0-86-U, circa 1986; 21
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0022)
  - WDIV-Tiger Promo, Chet Lemon, :30; Mobius category: 68; Mobius identifier: XT1229-68-0-86-U, circa 1986; 22
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0024)
  - Vlasic, Store, :10; Mobius category: 19; Mobius identifier: XT1238-19-0-86-U, circa 1986; 23
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0026)
  - Water Flexible Wear, :30; Mobius category: 85; Mobius identifier: XT1475-85-0-86-U, circa 1986; 24
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0027)
  - The Clean Look - Editorial, :30; Mobius category: 85; Mobius identifier: XT1468-85-0-86-U, circa 1986; 25
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0029)
  - T.V. Room, :30; Mobius category: 85; Mobius identifier: XT1470-85-0-86-U, circa 1986; 26
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0030)
  - Nissan, Miami Sound Machine-60ss, Pick-Up 30ss, Sentra 30ss; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT782ABC-81-0-86-U, circa 1986; 27
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0031)
  - Cetegory #81, Overall Production (Campaign), "Handwarmin's Back", "Jump to It", "Hot n Beefy"; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT1070ABC-81-0-86-U, circa 1986; 28
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0032)
  - Category 81 -- Campaign Series (3), "Annual Report" :60, "Merger" :60, "Capital Investment" :30; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT847ABC-81-0-86-U, circa 1986; 29
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0033)
  - Title: "Appointment Book" :60, Category: 86. Talent, Client: Church of Latter Day Saints; Mobius category: 86; Mobius identifier: XT1662-86-0-86-U, circa 1986; 30
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0034)
  - Pinnacle 384, :30; Mobius category: 85; Mobius identifier: XT1473-85-0-86-U, circa 1986; 31
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0035)
  - Peace Shield :30, Strategic Defense Initiative; Mobius category: 69; Mobius identifier: XT382-69-0-86-U, circa 1986; 32
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 64, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0037)
  - Serralles, Ron Palo Viejo, Orgullo 60ss, Paloma 30ss, Gallo 30ss; Mobius category: 84; Mobius identifier: XT783ABC-84-0-86-U, circa 1986; 33
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0042)
  - Single Entires, Nissan, Miami Sound Machine, :60; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT790-81-0-86-U, circa 1986; 34
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0043)
  - Category 81 -Overall Production, "Hot N Beefy"; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT1074-81-0-86-U, circa 1986; 35
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0044)
  - CBS Evening News with Dan Rather, Promo, "Americans"; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT740-81-0-86-U, circa 1986; 36
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0045)
  - Marlowe's Women Campaign, :25, :25, :70, category 81; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT716ABC-81-0-86-C, circa 1986; 37
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0048)
  - Summer Celebration Campaign, :90 / :30 / :60; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT712ABC-81-0-86-U, circa 1986; 38
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0049)
  - Marlowe's Women Campaign, :25, :25, :70, category 84; Mobius category: 84; Mobius identifier: XT720ABC-84-0-86-C, circa 1986; 39
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0050)
  - Wed Net A&P of 8/26, Reading PSA, :30; Mobius category: 71; Mobius identifier: XT517-71-U-87-U, 1987 August 26; 40
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0040)
  - Saatchi, Saatchi, Compton Inc, National Down Syndrome, SOC, "Peter Pan", XXCO 2123, :30; Mobius category: 71; Mobius identifier: XT540-71-U-87-U, 1987 September 21; 41
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0039)
  - Breckenridge Ski, "Front Range II" (Price Call) :30; Mobius category: 52; Mobius identifier: XT594-52-U-87-U, 1987 September 29; 42
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0041)
  - Factory, :30; Mobius category: 24; Mobius identifier: XT166-24-0-87-U, circa 1987; 43
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0038)
  - School Bus Safety PSA, For: Cal. State Auto Association, :30; Mobius category: 71; Mobius identifier: XT1146-71-U-87-U, circa 1987; 44
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0046)
  - Expo 86, Public Service Announcements, 3 by 30 seconds; Mobius category: 71; Mobius identifier: XT963ABC-71-U-87-C, circa 1987; 45
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 87, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0047)